noobpreneur.com 2011-05-25

# Privacy Policy | Noobpreneur Business Blog

Privacy Policy for www.Noobpreneur.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.noobpreneur.com/contact/).

At www.Noobpreneur.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.Noobpreneur.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.Noobpreneur.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Information collected by third-parties**  
We may allow third-party companies that use tracking technologies, such as cookies or pixels, to record IP information about users who visit or interact with our website. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.Noobpreneur.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.Noobpreneur.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….   
Google Adsense, Share-a-Sale, Commission Junction, Clickbank, Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.Noobpreneur.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.Noobpreneur.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.Noobpreneur.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Business Resources

 **Download Hundreds of Complimentary Industry Resources**  
Get hundreds of popular Industry magazines, white papers, webinars, podcasts, and more; all available at no cost to you. With more than 600 complimentary offers, you'll find plenty of titles to suit your professional interests and needs. [Click Here and Sign up today!](http://noobpreneur.tradepub.com/c/pubRD.mpl/?sr=ps&_t=ps:w_paraA:&ch=noobpren&_m=01.00ev.1.0.0&ct=Small&flt=all)

  * Visit DirectoryDaily.com for [directory reviews](http://directorydaily.com/) and updates on directory business from the web.
  * [Business Promotional Products](http://www.promodirect.com/ccc1007-business-26-food-gifts.htm) with low price guarantee! Get special offers and discounts only at Promo Direct.
